Guide to the Rice University Sallyport photo files, 1987-2003 UA 199
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Sallyport photo files, 1987-2003
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University
UA 199
3 Linear Feet (6 boxes)
Photographs featured in the Rice University alumni magazine, the Sallyport, 1987-2003. The Sallyport was first published in 1945 and is still published today as Rice Magazine.
Biographical / Historical
The Sallyport was first published in 1945 and is still published today. It is the longest running Rice publication and serves as a record of Rice people, events, trends and discoveries. In 2008 the name changed to Rice Magazine. It is published by the Office of Public Affairs of Rice University and is sent to university alumni, faculty, staff, graduate students, parents of undergraduates and friends of the university.
Scope and Contents
Photographs featured in the Rice University alumni magazine, the Sallyport, 1987-2003.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored offsite at the Library Service Center and require 24-hour notice for retrieval. Please contact the Woodson Research Center at 713-348-2586 or woodson@rice.edu for more information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This material was transferred to the Fondren Library from the Rice University Office of Public Affairs.
Related Materials
Many more sources of Rice University photographs are available at the Woodson Research Center.
Index Terms
Subjects
Universities and colleges; Social life and customs
Document Types
photographs
Subjects (Corporations)
Rice University
- Series I: 1987-1989, 115656
  - June-Aug. 1987, 108164 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Photographs and negatives include: David Scott, John Boles, Beer Bike, Regina Cavanaugh, and Sanford Higginbotham.
  - Sept./Oct. 1987, 108165 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Photographs and negatives include: Move-in, matriculation, O-Week, Michael Heizer Public Art, Craig Anderson, Rebecca Darrer, Susan Baker, and football.
  - Nov. 1987-Jan. 1988, 108166 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Photographs and negatives include: Tom Senning, Houston Children's Museum, Rice Outreach Day, basketball, Scott Thompson, Stephen Sain, Amber Wong, George Sun, and Charlotte Sun.
  - Feb./March 1988, 108167 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - April/May 1988, 108168 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - June-August 1988, 108169 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Fall 1988, 108170 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Winter 1989, 108171 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Spring/Summer 1989, 108172 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Summer 1989, 108173 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Fall 1989, 108174 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Series II: 1990-1999, 115657
  - Winter 1990, 108175 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Spring/Summer 1990, 108176 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Summer 1990, 108177 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Fall 1990, 108178 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Winter 1991, 108179 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - August 1991, 108180 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - October 1991, 108181 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - December 1991, 108182 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Feb./March 1992, 108183 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - April/May 1992, 108184 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - June/July 1992, 108185 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Aug./Sept. 1992, 108186 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Oct./Nov. 1992, 108187 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Dec. 1992/Jan. 1993, 108188 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Feb./March 1993, 108189 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - April/May 1993, 108190 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - June/July 1993, 108191 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Aug./Sept. 1993, 108192 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Oct./Nov. 1993, 108193 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Dec. 1993/Jan. 1994, 108194 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Feb./March 1994, 108195 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - April/May 1994, 108196 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - June/July 1994, 108197 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Aug./Sept. 1994, 108198 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Winter 1994/1995, 108199 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Feb./March 1995, 108200 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Fall 1995, 108201 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Spring 1995, 108202 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Summer 1995, 108203 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Fall 1998, 108204 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Spring 1999, 108205 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Series III: 2002-2003 and subject folders, 115658
  - Spring 2003, 108206 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Economic Summit 1990, 108207 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Architectural Details, 108208 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Campus scenes, 108209 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Chavanne, Harry, 108210 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Class individuals, 108211 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Biosciences professors, 108212 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Faculty, 108213 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - People, 108214 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Mouton, Onezieme, 2002; 115655 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - LEGO lab, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Recknagel, Marcia, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Martel College opening dedication, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Lopez, Elba, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Anderson-McAllen table, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Oshman Engineering Design Kitchen (OEDK) (images on disk) (Box 6)
  - John and Paula Hutchinson (Brown College masters) (image on disk) (Box 6)
  - MTV students (images on disk) (Box 6)
  - Lovett Hall (image on disk) (Box 6)